TOMAS OSLIAK

Web Developer **UI/UX** Designer



O MNE

Hello, my name is Tomáš Olšiak and I am 26 years old. I am currently working as a freelancer. Since 2023, I decided to change my priorities and started learning to program, while web development appealed to me the most. I started learning from the basics of HTML, CSS, JS until I progressed to React and Next.js, which I really like and would like to stay with. I am looking for a stable job where I will work with the given technologies that I enjoy and I will improve in them.

EXPERIENCES

Developer - Freelancer

JANUARY 2024 - Actual

Operator sewage treatment

KOLIBA, a.s., Hriňová, Slovak Republic MAY 2021 - JUNE 2023

Food handling

The company Pamons s.r.o JULY 2017 - MAR 2021

Merchandiser

Index Nosluš JULY 2016 - AUG 2016

HOBBY



Cycling



Skiing





Games

Traveling

EDUCATION

UNITED SECONDARY SCHOOL

CNC machinist | 2014-2018 Detva, Slovak Republic

KNOWLEDGE

- HTML,CSS,SCSS,JavaScript,Typescript
- React, Next, MongoDB, FireBase
- Tailwind,Bootstrap
- SolideWorks
- PHP. NODE.JS.
- Figma,Canva,UI/UX,Node.js,MUI,Shadcn,
- DaisyUI, Redux, Zustand, AWS SDK
- Git, GitHub, GitLab
- Cypress
- Microsoft Word, Excel
- O Driving license category B

LANGUAGES

- Slovak
- Czech
- German
- English

CONTACT

(a) +421 915 515 974

Detvianska Huta 364 96205

tomasolsiak1@gmail.com

www.tomasolsiak.porfolio.sk

https://github.com/katzohub